{
    "subject": "resource/Blick_am_Abend",
    "predicate": "ontology/language",
    "object": "resource/German_language",
    "human_readable": "Blick am Abend is written in German.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9725856781005859,
            "question": "Is Blick am Abend a German publication?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.959144115447998,
            "question": "Why might Blick am Abend be written in German?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9402390718460083,
            "question": "Are there any notable characteristics of German writing style evident in Blick am Abend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8914235234260559,
            "question": "Would someone who speaks German be able to understand Blick am Abend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8042218685150146,
            "question": "How does the use of German in Blick am Abend influence its readership?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7930070757865906,
            "question": "What language is Blick am Abend written in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.517752468585968,
            "question": "What other languages might Blick am Abend be published in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4453871250152588,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the language used in Blick am Abend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4260248839855194,
            "question": "Is Blick am Abend a multilingual publication?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3047820031642914,
            "question": "Could you provide examples of words or phrases from Blick am Abend?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Blick am Abend is written in German.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8524_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Blick am Abend a multilingual publication?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8524_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about the language used in Blick am Abend?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8524_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other languages might Blick am Abend be published in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8524_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8524_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8524_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8524_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8524_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8524_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8524_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8524_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8524_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8524_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8524_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the document mentions \"Blick am Abend\" as one of the major Swiss newspapers, and later provides translations into English language. Additionally, the document includes definitions and examples of the word \"blick\" in German, which implies that the newspaper is written in German."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that \"Blick am Abend\" is a Swiss newspaper, and several references are made to its content being available for translation from German, indicating it is originally written in German."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}